[buzzer beeps]
-[crowd cheering]
-[rhythmic thudding]
[crowd chanting]
Roots run deep.
-Roots run deep.
-[thudding stops]
Roots run deep. [cheering]
Roots run deep.
-[Mom] Will!
-Come on, Mom.
-We're almost there.
-[Mom] Will!
-[Mom] You're so fast.
-Mom, there it is.
[Mom] I can't keep up.
You need to be in the Olympics.
Let's go, Mom. We're so close.
[Will] Thank you for taking me
to see Jett's new billboard.
-Jett's huge!
-[Mom] Will, say "cheese."
-Will for three. [chuckles]
-[Mom chuckles] Ah, ah, ah.
Okay, boy, don't be doing
all of that now.
All right.
Guess it's time to go.
You have to go to work, right?
[Mom] Whoa, whoa, whoa.
[exhales] One second.
-Wait, turn it around.
-[camera beeps]
I got it! There we go. Okay.
How about you and I
watch the Thorns
from inside the stadium?
'Cause I'm taking my baby
to see his very first,
yep, roarball game!
[exclaims]
[stammers] What?
[gasps]
Is this for real?
I mean... [chuckles]
...unless you're busy?
[sobs]
Oh, baby.
Aw, it's okay.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I love you, Mom.
I love you too, Will.
Let's go, Mom. Come on.
-Roots run deep.
-[fan] Yeah, let's go!
Oh. It's right here.
Right here. Come on.
Mom, stop it.
[both] Whoo! Let's go!
Whoo! Let's go!
[announcer]
Welcome to the Greenhouse!
-It's starting!
-[buzzer beeps]
[announcer] Are you ready?
-[voice 1] Who is the GOAT?
-[voice 2] Who is the GOAT?
-[voice 3] Who's the GOAT?
-[voice 4] Who's the GOAT?
[voice 2]
Who is truly the GOAT?
♪ Yeah, thinkin' that it
Happened overnight, it didn't ♪
♪ In it for the long-haul
Flight, committed ♪
♪ Look, wait ♪
[roars]
[announcer] Introducing
Vineland's very own,
the hometown hero,
a five-time all-star,
Jett Fillmore.
-Yeah! Let's go, Vineland.
-[crowd cheering]
Let's go, Jett! [chuckles]
Having a good time, Will? Baby?
[Will gasps]
[Will] That's gonna be me, Mom.
When I get big,
I'm gonna be just like her.
[upbeat music playing]
[horns honking]
[Will pants]
One... Yeah!
It's the power of the mind.
Your body's not tired.
You can take a break.
Don't take a break.
[panting]
You got this.
Keep pushing.
-Keep pushing.
-[music ends]
-[chuckling]
-[yelps]
[gerbil] I'm okay!
[Will grunts]
Hey, Will. Are you working out?
Hey, Theo. You know it.
Jett Fillmore doesn't take
a day off, and neither do I.
My dad said
you can't play roarball
'cause you're too small.
[Will groans]
Everyone says that, Theo.
When I'm on the Thorns,
you'll be courtside,
my bro-dent. [chuckles]
Heck, yeah.
Go, Thorns! [chuckles]
[phone beeps]
[Will] No rest for the ballers.
Hey! Will!
I hope you're not trying to
sneak out... [chuckles]
...without paying your rent.
Ooh. Yeah. Um...
I'll get it to you
as soon as you, uh,
fix those holes
in the ceiling.
What holes? [screams]
Gotta go to work.
Catch you later, Frank.
[grunting] Will!
[horn honks]
Good morning, Vineland!
[commuter] Whoever said that,
be quiet, please.
[Will] Roots run deep!
[all] Roots run deep!
Welcome back.
Tonight,
it's Jett Fillmore, the vet,
taking on Mane Attraction,
the champ.
The GOAT debate starts here.
Thorns versus Magma.
Go Magma! Go Shivers!
Yeah, go whoever is playing
the Thorns. I-I don't care.
Gerald!
I'm gonna kick you out
if you keep wearing
the other teams' jerseys.
Carol, I'm the ultimate hater.
No pie for you.
Sheep. She took my pie.
[grunts]
The Thorns have broken his
heart one too many times.
This is Vineland, Gerald.
We never give up.
We've always got hope.
The Thorns, they just ne
to draft your boy.
I'll turn things around
real quick.
So, they're drafting
delivery goats now?
[scoffs, chuckles]
[Carol] I need one
to deliver food.
Ooh! About that, Ms. Carol,
uh, can I get a raise?
You want a raise?
Tell the Thorns
to win a few games
so we can get the crowds
back in here.
I remember when
Jett was a rookie.
This place used to be full.
Before we realized she was
never gonna win us a Claw?
Uh, Carol, can I have
my pie back, please?
Keep talking. I'll cut you off
from ice cream too.
Be careful with these.
Oh. Got it.
Oh. Moe needs more coffee,
and the out-of-towners,
they want their check.
How do you always do that?
Freaks me out every time.
Hey, I'm a goat.
I see everything.
["Best Day" playing]
Pass it, Will.
Okay!
Hey, guys.
Got it!
See you later, Will!
[announcer]
Thorns are already down by 20.
Oh, come on.
[customer 1] Up here.
[trumpets]
All right. Let's do this.
♪ No worries
Up inside my mind ♪
-[customer 1] Thank you.
-I got you.
♪ This is the best day
Of my life ♪
[groans, blows raspberries]
♪ This is the best day
Of my life ♪
Step back. Yes!
[cheering]
-[customer 2] Thank you.
-[customer 3] Thank you.
-[customer 4] Thank you.
-[customer 5] Thank you.
-Here you go.
-Appreciate you.
[screams]
[chuckling]
♪ This is the best day
Of my life ♪
[music ends]
My mammal. Finally, bro.
Chill, Daryl.
You ordered a water.
Water is food too, bro.
[Will] So, Hannah,
how's Jett doing?
Mane's kind of
working Jett tonight.
I hate to say it,
she might be washed.
You serious? Jett can handle
that one-trick pony.
Um, is his one trick
being the best at roarball?
He's got the shooting,
the passing...
Picture-perfect pecs.
Luxurious locks.
Mane is pretty much him.
-[commentator] Oh, my!
-[both exclaim]
Mane Attraction just put...
On her head!
...the former number-one pick,
Olivia Burke...
That's not good.
...on a poster.
-[phone beeps]
-[gasps] No way.
[Will] Oh,
there's already memes?
Oh, "poster child"?
Now, that's rough.
Yeah, that was
so not cool.
[sighs] All right. I'm out.
I'm gonna go train
at the Cage.
What? You're not gonna
watch the game with us?
Nah, I gotta go
while the Cage is empty,
'cause after the game,
you know it's gonna fill up.
Do not let Grizz catch you.
[slurps]
Oh, I won't.
[crowd members]
Roots run deep. Roots run deep.
[melancholy music playing]
[exhales]
Step back. Jett!
[cheering]
The crowd goes wild.
["Parade" playing]
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ It won't rain on my parade ♪
♪ Oh, let it rain, ooh ♪
[cheers]
Another one. [cheers]
With only five seconds left,
the ball goes to Harris.
He's all alone.
Three, two, one...
[music ends]
[sighs]
What's going on here, folks?
They're resetting the clock?
Don't question it.
He's got time
for one more shot.
Three, two, one...
[dramatic music playing]
-[horn blares]
-[crowd cheering]
[kisses]
[crowd members] Roots run deep.
Roots run deep. Roots run deep.
Roots run deep.
One day, baby. [kisses]
One day.
[exclaims]
[chuckling]
Get that weak sauce
up out of here.
Yo, what's your problem, Grizz?
Every day you're here.
Every day I gotta kick you out.
I mean,
what are the rules, y'all?
[all] Smalls can't ball.
First off, I'm not a small.
I'm a medium.
-What? Medium fries?
-[chuckling]
You will never make it
into Roar.
I mean, come on. Let me run.
I'm better than
half of y'all anyways.
Let me show you what I got.
[scoffs] Ball me.
Only thing you're running
is off this court.
Now get out of here.
[scoffs] Whatever.
Good night, Shirley.
You're in my house now.
[players cheering]
[commentator]
And that's the game.
Thorns lose by 26.
Clock's ticking, Jett.
Jett, Jett, Jett,
hey, can you sign this for me?
Of course. Anything for a fan.
There you go, kid.
Thanks, Jett.
Why can't you win
a championship?
Retire already!
Jett, could we take a photo?
Jett, third loss in a row.
How does it feel?
Flo? Where's Flo?
When are we
gonna stop sucking?
Flo!
Hey. Flo?
Who's seen Flo?
[growls]
["Mamacitas" playing]
[inhales deeply, moans]
[grunting]
[snorts, exhales]
[chuckles]
Hey, there, grumpy cat.
[growling]
How'd the game end?
[all scream]
I stopped watching
and punched myself
in the face instead. [laughs]
You think this is funny?
You're the team owner, Flo.
How am I supposed to win
when you've got me surrounded
by head cases and has-beens?
Hey, I'm working on it.
We don't even have
a sixth player, Flo,
but you got
your hooves done.
Listen here, Jett,
free agents aren't free. Okay?
So unless you have
a sixth player in mind
who can fill an arena
and doesn't want
a big, fat check,
I'm gonna get back
to my mud bath, okay?
Oh, that is hogwash.
It's your job
to figure it out.
Trade players,
sell the team...
I don't care what you
got to do. Just do it. Now.
Careful what
you wish for, Jett.
[thudding]
[gasps]
[screams, groans]
He's fine.
[atmospheric music playing]
Hey, I'm driving here.
Get out of the road, ya medium.
[whispers] Keep it down.
Why are you so loud?
[groans]
[Frank] Hello, William.
Hey, Frank. How are you?
Would you happen to have
that rent?
Oh. Oh, yeah, yeah.
Right. Right.
Frank, I got you.
It's all right here.
I meant to give it
to you today actually
22, 23...
This is not actual money,
this piece of paper.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
What about last month's
and the month before?
Frank, it's me. Come on.
I just need
a little more time.
You had time, Will.
I got mouths to feed.
I don't need one more.
-Hey, Will.
-Hey, guys.
-Hey, Will. Hey, Will.
Hey, Will.
Hey, Will. Hey, Will.
[Will] Y'all are still awake?
-Hey, Will.
-Oh, what's up, Theo?
Did they let you play
at the Cage today?
You know me. I'm working on it.
That's a lot of kids.
Indeed it is.
I'm sorry, kiddo.
Look, get me my rent money
by tomorrow
or I gotta rent the room to
somebody else.
Capisce?
Will, I forgot to tell you--
[Frank] Hey, kids, come on.
Get in the tub.
Here we go, here we go.
[sighs]
[sighs] Whatever.
You need money?
Well, you're in luck
'cause you can start earning
up to 300 bucks per day.
How? By trading crypto
on BigBroncoCrypto...
[wife] Frank,
I'm pregnant again.
[Frank]
That's amazing, sweetheart.
[chuckling] You know,
we needed another one of those.
-Hey, Will...
-[knocking on wall]
...gonna need that rent money.
[upbeat music playing]
♪ You hoopin', we hoopin'
You shootin', I'm shootin' ♪
-♪ That glass, we crashin' ♪
-♪ Say what ♪
-♪ That pass, fantastic ♪
-♪ Okay ♪
♪ You'd better
Tie them shoes up ♪
-[music ends]
-[Will] Boom!
Check these out.
Vineland green, Fillmore Fours,
in the flesh.
Jett wore these
in the Furball game.
Normally,
these sell for around six...
[inhales deeply]
...but I'll give it to you
for five.
No, not the Fours.
[exhales deeply]
Oh, I wanted those.
But you're broke.
But if I had the Fours
I wouldn't look it.
Ah. Yes. Yes, you would.
It's gonna be okay.
Pristine upper mesh.
Taut laces.
Mmm. [smacks lips]
Nutty.
[Hannah] Nasty.
250.
Come on.
250? How dare you.
[grunts]
[Hannah] The disrespect.
Come on, Will.
I can do installments.
Yeah, that's great, Dary
but my landlord can't.
[exhales] Okay.
I can't watch this.
So, 400?
240.
I-It's going down?
230.
Dang, stop!
-Please, please!
-[phone chimes]
Yo!
[gasps] No way!
Y'all are not
gonna believe this.
Mane is at the Cage,
and he's taking on
all challengers.
So, we, uh,
doing this or what?
[sighs] Okay, fine.
All right. Let's dip.
["Hooligang" playing]
[both grunting]
[whinnies]
-[groans]
-Whoo!
Who's got next?
♪ No, nobody can
Do it like me ♪
♪ Zoo Pals plate
With the Kid Cuisine ♪
Now watch this.
Give me that.
♪ 360s in my green machine ♪
Garbage.
I said, who's got next?
I can't hear nothing.
Where y'all at?
Who got next?
[Grizz] Hey, yo. Check ball.
Yeah!
Get him, Grizz!
Got a piece of
flaming garbage over here.
Touch me. Touch me.
[exclaims]
[music ends]
[groans, distorted]
[chuckles] Yeah!
Get lost, Mane, you're a bum.
Seriously? You mean to tell me
this is the best
Vineland's got?
I thought the Cage
is where roarball was born.
[whinnies]
I guess this town's only as
weak as its greatest player.
[scoffs] Hey, where she at?
If Jett's nowhere to be found,
then somebody gotta answer me.
-Who's got next?
-[Will] I got next.
Who said that?
[Will] Hey!
Nobody talks about Jett
and Vineland like that.
Excuse me. Pardon.
Hey, move out the way.
-I got next.
-[crowd gasping]
Check up.
Wait, wait, a goat?
[laughing]
[all laughing]
Thank you for the laugh,
little dude,
but, uh, why don't you
just run on back
to the kiddie pool
or something.
Get you an ice cream.
But, seriously, any takers?
[Will]
Even if I put money on it?
First the shoes,
now your rent money?
Yes, Will. Commit.
[crowd member 1] Oh, Mane,
what are you gonna do now?
[crowd member 2] Where's all
the big talk now, Mane?
[crowd member 3]
Let's go, Vineland!
Oh. So this is all the gre
Vineland has to offer?
A goat and some spare change?
[chuckles]
But you know what?
Mane doesn't duck smoke
so check up.
-Let's do it.
-[camera shutters clicking]
Everything counts
as one.
First to three.
Your ball.
-[whinnies, snorts]
-[crowd gasping]
[both chuckling]
-Oh, snap!
-[Will] That's one.
I'd fight a big for that.
-[upbeat music playing]
-[grunts]
Oh. So you do know how to pass.
You gonna guard me
from all the way out there?
[snorts]
Let's go.
Come on.
[both grunting]
[Mane] When I get
that ball, it's over.
Whoa! [whinnies, distorted]
[crowd clamoring]
[laughing]
You got owned by a goat!
-Oh, shoot!
-Hey!
This goat out here!
This dude's eating beans!
[both chuckling]
-[cheering]
-[grunts]
[snorts, grunts]
[camera shutters clicking]
All right. Let's get serious.
Looks like you're gonna make me
take my chains off.
Yeah, man. Take it all off.
[groans]
[chuckles]
Oh, okay. I see.
You're an outside
shooter, huh?
Now get past me.
Oh. [chuckles]
Now we playing for real.
This is how it feel
in the league.
This is my house.
[chuckles]
You're mine now.
[chuckling]
Boom!
[chuckles, exclaims]
Boom shakalaka!
[groans]
Ooh.
Fool, I wasn't helping you up.
-I just wanted my cash.
-[groans]
Thanks.
[crowd clamoring]
-Hey! We got goat money.
-[all cheering]
That wasn't bad.
Everyone didn't have their
phones out for that long.
Right, Daryl?
Yes, they did.
[suspenseful music playing]
[sighs] Come on. Come on.
[both screaming]
[grunts, gasps]
What?
I respect that.
Hey, Will.
Will, uh, I'm really sorry
about my dad.
But I want you to know
I believe in you.
Oh! Oh!
And I made you
a sandwich. Catch!
[majestic music plays, stops]
Oops. Airball.
Sorry about that. [sighs]
[sighs] Don't even
worry about it.
[Theo] I'll still see you
at the Greenhouse
when you're playing for
the Thorns!
Thanks, Theo.
Good luck!
Yo, I told you
that video was crazy.
Yeah, that dude was guzzling.
Yo! What's up, my mammal?
[Hannah] Hey.
Oh, hey.
[Hannah] There he is.
Thanks for letting me
crash at your place.
[Daryl] You brought your stuff?
Hey, throw it on the pile.
Still haven't cleaned.
Okay, just pick a pile.
They're all filthy.
Now quit your yapping
and come check out
what I've been cooking up.
[video game music playing]
[Daryl, Hannah chuckling]
[chuckling continues]
[automated voice] Will wins!
Oh, you like that?
Come on,
this is gonna go viral.
You broke his ankles.
Yeah, and he broke my horn.
Ugh. Will, look,
you wanted footage
of you playing against big
And you just went up against
the biggest,
baddest in all of roarball.
Yep, yep. Facts.
You did that, Will.
[sighs]
Okay.
Well, I'm just gonna
make this one live
'cause I think Daryl
just farted. Ugh.
I'll see you both later.
-I got a date. Need to shave.
-[both] Ooh!
With who?
Oh, I didn't tell you?
Your mom. [chuckling]
Oh, shoot.
Yeah, she got you, bro.
Okay, okay. Wasn't even funny.
Hey, bro.
Wanna play some Roar 2K?
Nah, think I'm good.
Should probably
call it a night, you know?
No, sure thing. Yeah,
make yourself comfortable.
I'm gonna get on these sticks.
[clears throat] Hello!
[screaming]
Okay.
[groans]
Ugh. [sighs]
[train rumbling]
[horn blaring]
[upbeat music playing]
It's him, look.
Look, it's totally him!
[all cheering]
Hey! What's up, buddy?
Hey, Will.
-Hey, Will.
-Hi, anonymous animal.
Look, Mom. It's Will.
-I'm sorry.
-That's okay. It's okay.
Yo, who is the clown
that parked like that outside?
[music ends]
Everybody good?
-[clears throat]
-[trumpets]
Why are y'all not blinking?
That's me, sweetheart.
I'm the clown.
[stammers]
You're Florence Everson!
You're the owner of the Thorns!
You can ignore
all the voicemails, Mr. Harris.
It looks like
I found you myself.
She's been waiting for you.
Without ordering anything.
Sit.
You had quite the game
yesterday.
You broke Mane's ankles
so hard,
I thought they were gonna
have to put him down!
And the Internet just
loved it. [chuckles]
-They love you.
-[clicks]
Yo! That's crazy! [chuckles]
Oh, it gets crazier.
Will, maybe you
haven't noticed,
but the team is awful.
Oh, no. We trash.
We have the league's
best player
and no path
to the Claw, again...
Small to small,
I believe you are exactly
what Jett and this team
needs right now.
Goat, sure.
But I think you might be
a two-horned unicorn.
-Really?
-[chuckles] Yeah.
-I'd like to make you an offer.
-[clicks]
We need a sixth player
to join the Thorns for
the back half of the seaso
[gasps] Oh, my gosh.
[stammers] Is it really--
Is it finally happening?
I just need you to sign here,
some initials here,
and you're officially a Thorn.
And, uh, Jett.
She signed off on this?
In many ways,
it was her idea. Yeah.
So what's it gonna be?
Play for Vineland, or stay here
and bus my table?
Pen. Pen! Pen.
Someone give me a pen!
I don't have a-- Ow!
Thank you.
W. H.
Where there's a Will,
there's a way.
Oh, congratulations, sweetie.
We're so proud of you.
[all chanting]
Will! Will! Will! Will! Will!
I cannot believe it!
I'm gonna be a Vineland Thorn!
-Breaking news!
-You're not gonna believe it!
-Will, it went viral!
-It certainly did.
I'm so excited, Will.
-Who's the fancy pig?
-[Will chuckles]
I hate this town.
-[alarm beeping]
-[Jett grunting]
[groans]
[grunts]
-[grunts]
-[spine cracking]
Oh. It hurts. It hurts.
-[sighs]
[licking]
Welcome to the Roar Roundup.
I'm two-time champion, Chuck,
alongside my cohost,
itty-bitty-bitey-buddy,
Rusty.
Rusty! [chuckles]
I can't wait till they put
you out to pasture, Chuck.
[chuckles] That's good.
Well, but back to the question
we ask every season.
[Rusty] Can you be the GOAT
without winning a championship?
-Uh, yeah.
-[spine clicks]
-[Chuck] Claws make careers.
-What is that?
-[Rusty] You don't say!
-Nuh-uh.
I feel for Fillmore. She's
always been a great player,
but Father Time
catches up with everyone.
Without me, they wouldn't
have anything to talk about.
[Chuck] All stats, no Claws.
But you can't
put all the blame on her.
Anyone who's watched this team
and thinks Jett's the biggest
problem is blind as a--
Blind as a what, Chuck?
Say it. Blind as a what?
I am the all-time
leading scorer in Roar history.
[Rusty] Speaking of the Thorns,
we've got some
breaking news, Chuck!
The Vineland Thorns have
finally signed a sixth player.
Looks like they're finally
getting Jett some help.
Yes! A crocodile?
No, no, no, no.
Bigger. A gorilla?
[Rusty] We go now to
owner Florence Everson...
That's what I'm talking about.
...with an exclusive interview.
We signed
roarball's first small.
A small what?
We got a little...
A little, uh, what?
-...teeny...
-A what now?
-...tiny...
-Come again.
-...goat.
-[goat bleats]
A goat?
[growling]
[engine revs]
Oh, not again.
-Florence Marjorie Everson!
-[glass smashes]
You're signing a goat?
Have you lost your mind?
Okay. Excuse me.
You're the one who asked for
a team who could win the Claw
and you didn't care how.
Remember?
Well, I care about this.
I can't play with a goat.
He's an embarrassment
to the team.
to the city. He's a--
Uh... He's sitting
right there.
Hey!
You gotta be kidding me.
I couldn't even see him
in the chair, Flo.
How am I supposed to
see him on the court?
I'll be the goat
in the Thorns jersey.
You feel me?
Uh-huh.
Look away, Flo.
I'm just gonna eat him.
Yeah, I'm gonna eat him
with a side of ranch dressing,
and we're gonna act
like none of this happened.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I do not taste good.
I-I thought you said
she knew.
It's my job to bend
the truth, Will. Come on.
[meows, growls]
It's also my job
to play the long game.
This is generating
more attention
than we have had in years.
You don't want him
on the court, that's your call.
-But he stays on the roster.
-[Jett growling]
Oh, you must have
lost your mind.
Put your paw down.
[sighs]
You should be elated.
The stars have
aligned perfectly
because the press is
dying to meet Will.
Will, down. Get down.
[Will] Oh, okay.
And I want you
to introduce him.
No. Not happening.
Yes, you are.
They're actually waiting
for you right downstairs.
So keep them
tails up high, yes?
Big smiles!
Love you both! Now get out!
-Jett, hey.
-[sighs]
I just wanted you to know,
this is my dream come true.
I mean, to play with you, like,
my favorite player of all time.
I know I'm not
what you expected,
but I've spent my whole life
training for this moment.
And if you just give me a sho--
Look, kid. I saw
your little viral video.
Mane baked you
like a birthday cake.
Yeah, yeah, no.
I'm gonna enjoy
watching the piranhas
eat you alive.
-Jett! Over here! Jett!
-Hey, Jett! Over here!
-Will! Will!
-Will, over here!
-Will!
-Will, Will, Will!
-[Will grunts]
-[chair squeaking]
[chair squeaking]
[scoffs]
[chair rattles, clicks]
[chair squeaking]
Let's get started.
Hardest questions first.
Do you think going viral
in a playground entitles you
to play professional roarball?
Do you worry you'll let
other smalls down?
Aren't you just
a shameless publicity stunt
to distract from another
Thorns losing season?
[reporter 1]
Are you actually a goat?
[reporter 2]
Don't you just kinda suck?
I... Sorry. Can--
Can you repeat the questio
Hey, hey. One at a time, y'all.
This boy is not even
media trained, okay?
So, Will. How does it feel
to be the first small ever
to sign a professional
roarball contract?
Uh, to be honest with you,
it's all kinda surreal.
I mean, last night
I was fighting off roaches
at my best friend's crib...
[crowd gasps]
...and now I'm playing
for the Thorns.
[groans]
You shouldn't have said that.
Will, we are getting word
that the roach community
was pretty offended
by your last comment.
Would you care to
issue an apology?
Oh, gosh. No, no, no, no.
That's not what I meant.
[stammers] I love roaches.
Lies.
-Can we, uh, move on
to the next question?
-Up here.
So, Will, you're not at all
concerned about being hurt?
Roarball takes its toll on
the toughest of bigs.
I imagine for a small,
-it could be fatal.
-[crowd gasping]
Uh, well...
No, no. Will knows the risks.
Could he be clobbered?
Possibly.
Crushed? Perhaps.
Killed? Probably.
[crowd gasps]
But that's how much
he loves the game.
He'd die for it.
[gulps]
Right, Will?
[chuckles] Right.
What about Mane?
Are you worried about a rematch
down the line?
No. No way.
We call this dude
the horse whisperer,
'cause he broke
that bronco's back, okay?
You know what
he was telling me earlier?
He's got a nickname for Mane.
-He calls him "My Little Pony."
-[crowd laughing]
Don't you?
No, I didn't say that.
You do.
I did not say that.
And he also said that Mane
definitely ain't the GOAT,
and his hair is wack, too,
which I also agree with.
Oh, he's dead.
-Why are you doing this to me?
-[reporter 3] Last question.
Uh, this one's for Jett.
You're in year fifteen.
The team's bringing on a goat
to solve its problems.
Do you ever wonder
if it's time to hang it up?
[chuckles] I'm not hanging up
anything, okay?
I feel great right now,
playing some of
the best ball of my career.
And please,
I've played with every mutt
this league has to offer.
My only concern
is going out there
and doing what I gotta do
to win the Claw,
and nothing,
and I mean nothing,
is gonna get
in the way of that.
Thank you.
Bagels on the third floor.
Jett, over here!
Yeah. Uh, cool.
[reporter 4] Will!
[reporter 5]
Do you have any comment?
I can-- Okay, thank you.
Bye.
[interviewer]
Coach Dennis, how do you plan
on utilizing the goat
in the rotation?
That's a great question.
Well--
[Jett] Dennis, he's all yours.
[Dennis]
Hey, Jett, you got a second?
I just wanted to
go over these new plays.
[clears throat, chuckles]
You heard me.
Uh, we'll do it later. [laughs]
How you doing, kid?
Dennis Cooper.
Pleased to meet you.
Oh, I know you,
Coach Dennis.
It's an honor.
Coach is a strong word.
I'm more of
an underpaid clipboard stand.
[chuckles] Whee!
But I keep trying.
Uh, let's get you suited up
for the game.
I'm ready to play.
Play? [chuckles]
I... That's cute. No.
What?
Nothing.
And here we are.
[majestic music playing]
No way. The Thorns locker room?
[squeals] Yes!
Get dressed
and come meet the team.
[giggles] Yes, yes, yes, yes!
This is crazy!
[gasps]
Yo! My name.
On a Thorns jersey.
Oh, wait. Fillmore 13's?
[giggles]
[exhales]
Not bad.
Right?
[Chuck] It's game night.
Welcome back to Regionally
Organized Animal Roarball.
The sport with
the wildest courts.
[Rusty] Stalactites.
Sandstorms.
Cliffs.
Ice.
Fire. And vines!
[Chuck] Tonight,
we're at the Greenhouse,
and the stadium is rocking
for the first
of three straight home games.
And no surprise,
the smalls have shown up big
-for Vineland's newest Thorn.
-[yelps]
♪ Y'all ready for this? ♪
[Rusty chuckling]
The Canoodle Cam is on patrol!
[Chuck giggles]
Somebunny's in love!
Looks like they're necking!
[Rusty] "Polly want a cracker?"
Am I right, up-Chuck? [laughs]
Oh, you caught it!
[chuckling]
I'm a genius.
Okay, Olivia.
Clear your mind.
I am in control.
I know who I am.
I am good enough.
I do not care about
the opinions of others.
I do not care what
they're saying about me online,
right now, across multiple
platforms which I could check,
just to see
what they're saying.
Phone! Phone.
Does anyone have a phone?
You're not even in uniform!
Ha! It's tear-away.
Oh, Lenny.
We're gonna get you!
[groaning]
Daddy's a yeti!
[chuckles] Listen. I celebrate
your creativity with the foam,
but it's not okay to shoot
Daddy in the face, okay? Great.
[giggling]
Cute kids.
Yeah, I know. Right?
Don't look now, but there's
a baby goat walking towards us
with a weird smile on his face.
Uh, I'm Will Harris.
Ready to help the team win
however I can.
Oh, look, a pre-game snack.
[gasps]
Let me just unhinge my jaw.
Please, please! No!
Don't eat me! Don't eat me!
It's the viral kid!
He's sick?
No, he went viral.
-Weird. I like it. Come. Dance.
-[mysterious music playing]
We're not doing
your little dance, Modo.
[team member] I kinda like it.
[rasping, chuckling]
[muttering]
Uh, what's with the egg?
-[shushing]
-[music stops]
Don't let them control you.
[chuckling, rasps]
[crowd chanting]
Roots run deep.
-Roots run deep.
-[rumbling]
It's really loud
in here, right? [groans]
Hey, Jett? Do you think I'll
get some playing time tonight?
[scoffs]
[announcer]
Introducing your newest Thorn.
-Coming in at a hot 5'7"...
-[crowd booing]
...from South Vineland,
the Mane-slayer himself,
Will Harris!
[booing continues]
Where'd he go?
I can't see him. [laughs]
Will history
be made tonight,
or will he follow in your
underwhelming footsteps, Chuck?
You suck, Rusty.
And yes, that was a bat joke.
Yeah! Let's go, Will!
Yeah, Will!
That's Will, right?
He kind of looks like a gerbil.
Do you think Will's gonna play?
I hope not, or we're gonna
watch that kid die on live TV.
[all] Gerald!
[growls]
-Great! Yes! There it is!
-Let's go, baby! Keep it up!
Hey, Coach, when do you think
I might get in?
-Just study the playbook, kid.
-End his bloodline!
Oh, story time?
Yeah. Bring it in. Once, there
was a play called Eagle 24.
-Oh, I like this one.
-[whistle blows]
Anyone tired? I could sub in.
-I could take a break.
-No.
He's gonna be playing in
the next game. Trust me.
We need a bucket here.
Modo, hang out on
the perimeter. Space the floor.
-Do your thing.
-[Modo rasps]
I always do.
Ball! Ball!
Ball! Ball! Ball! Ball!
Ball! Ball! [grunts]
Hey, I actually noticed that
the moose always drives right,
so if you just
shift the defense a li--
Who wants an acacia leaf break?
-[team member] Ooh, ooh. I do!
-[groans]
-[grunts, chuckles]
-[buzzer sounds]
Tomorrow, history
will be made. [chuckles]
And I mean it this time.
Shake it off, Archie!
I got water, towels,
emotional support.
I'm covered.
[Rusty] Three tough losses in
a row for the Vineland Thorns.
[Chuck] And now they'll
hit the road with a goat
who's yet to see
a dime of playing time.
-[spine clicks]
-Ouch. Ooh. [sighs]
[exhales]
[wheels squeaking]
No days off, am I right?
No, no, no. Nope.
This is
a private practice session.
Hey, watch this.
From the logo. Nothing but net.
[ball bouncing]
Hmm. Lucky shot.
Hmm. Maybe.
Bank shot.
[chuckling]
Should I play the lottery?
I'm feeling good today.
Why are you here, kid?
I want
some playing time.
[chuckles] Not happening.
Let's shoot for it.
Or are you scared
you're gonna lose to a goa
[chuckles] All right. Bet.
Top of the stands,
hook shot off the glass,
spin around the rim, in.
[upbeat music playing]
Jett from downtown.
[gasps] Did it.
Easy.
[Jett] Through the vines, in.
[blowing]
Hot paws over here.
Yeah, baby!
[scoffs]
[Will] What else you got?
Off the top,
in.
Ooh. [giggling]
[whistles]
[chuckling] Whoo-hoo!
[Will giggling]
[Jett] Hanging from the lights.
Easy.
[music stops]
Ooh!
You are mine now.
-[music resumes]
-[chuckling]
From the tunnel,
over the backboard,
nothing but net. All right?
If I hit this one,
you have to give me
playing time. Huh?
Okay, yeah. We'll see.
Pack it up.
[screams]
Ah. You missed. [chuckles]
[Dennis] Come on, we gotta fly.
Plane leaves in 30.
♪ Crazy ♪
♪ Wait till the world's
all mine ♪
♪ It's gonna be crazy ♪
♪ Crazy ♪
♪ Everything I survived
I must be crazy ♪
♪ Crazy ♪
[panting]
I really had to hustle
back there, but...
Yo! [stammers] What?
We're on a PJ?
-[chuckles]
-[song ends]
[gasps]
What? Oh, sick.
-[Olivia] Are you
seeing this? Oh, no.
-[child] You got dunked on!
Are y'all playing Roar 2K?
They've added memes?
I mean, why would they do that?
It's so disrespectful!
Not just to me...
[muffled] ...but to all birds.
Auntie Olivia
is not giving bird. Birds fly.
Are you broken?
Hey, hey, uh,
Auntie Olivia has a condition
called flightless bird
syndrome.
Aw. Auntie Olivia can't fly.
[both] But we can! [chuckling]
Oh, no! Not the cockpit!
Girls!
[child 1]
We're taking over this plane!
-[child 2] Reporting for duty!
-[Archie] No, don't touch that!
At least the bags are comfy.
Hey, Lenny.
Is this seat taken?
Yep.
By who?
[Lenny] By me.
-[exhales] Ooh, that's good.
-[squeaking]
Are you really trying to
body-shame me
for needing two seats?
Sorry. My bad.
-Hey, Modo. Is this seat taken?
-[rasping]
Eh.
Technically speaking, nah.
[squelching]
[screams]
What the... Ew.
Oh. [chuckling]
That's just my skin.
[yawns] I molted.
[exclaims, chuckles]
Ugh. Okay. There you go.
[snoring]
[groans]
Jett!
Hey.
So, you were shooting arou
with the kid.
[Will] Jett!
He's good, huh?
My mama could make
those shots, okay? [scoffs]
Doesn't mean
he can play. [chuckles]
Hey, Jett!
[grunts, sighs]
I made it. Huh?
[snoring continues]
Hey, everyone,
a round of applause.
Will made it.
Oh. Spicy.
Is following me around
being annoying
your full-time job,
or... [sputters]
You-You-You have to open it.
The nuts,
they're inside the can.
Wait. So the can
isn't the food?
[groans]
-[chuckles]
-[phone chimes]
Mane dropped a...
[gasps]
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Mane just dropped
a diss track about goat bo
Oh, Olivia,
put it on the big screen.
-Wait! No, wait.
-You got it, Miss Lady Girl.
-Modo's still sleeping.
-Actually, I'm wide awake.
I am here for this. Let's go!
[Will groans]
-Oh, yeah! Let's hear that one.
-Oh, no.
Oh, yes.
[Will] No, please!
No, no, no.
[hip-hop music playing]
[Mane] You're not ready.
It's Mane season! [chuckles]
You know what's in my cup!
♪ I know you think
You're all "ba-a-ad" ♪
♪ But I'ma have you crying
Like "ba-a-a" ♪
♪ You just goat here, I'm
The Mane Attraction, though ♪
♪ I'm the Godfather
Call me Pony Soprano ♪
♪ I'ma keep it short
Just like you ♪
♪ Next time we on the court
The smoke's on you ♪
♪ Act tough, but you're scared
I'm in your nightmares ♪
♪ Tonight, when you sleep
You'll be crying ♪
♪ Goat tears, goat tears ♪
♪ You'll be crying
Goat tears, goat tears ♪
[song ends]
-[Modo chuckles]
-[Olivia] Oh, that is a banger!
[Lenny] Eh,
the lyrics are kinda mid.
[team] ♪ You'll be crying
Goat tears, goat, goat ♪
♪ You'll be crying
Goat tears, goat ♪
♪ Tasty Goat, you'll be crying
[sighs]
[whirring, dings]
[upbeat music playing]
Yo!
It smells so good in here.
[beeps]
This... this is where
I wanna be at.
What is that? I've never...
This could be in a room?
Yeah, baby!
We chilling in a penthouse!
[singsongy]
We chilling in a penthouse.
We chilling in a pent...
-Oh! This is crazy!
-[phone ringing]
Hey! Look who it is!
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
You guys ain't gonna believe
this place.
Yo, bros, bros. We got a
95-inch TV in the living room.
You see that? Aight.
TV on the toilet.
Even has a remote.
-Unsanitary, but it's cool.
-[remote beeps]
[groans] Stop, stop, stop.
Bad toilet, bad toilet.
And last but not least,
TV in the minibar.
[Hannah, Daryl] Ooh!
[Hannah] So, what's up with
the floor seats?
You said courtside?
Well... [sighs]
...you know, with the way
things have been going,
if I'm even still on
the team in a week,
I mean, I'll try to
find you some tickets.
[blows raspberry]
Are you kidding me, bro?
What do you mean,
if you're going to be
on the team next week?
You're on the actual Thorns.
Ain't nobody kicking our boy
off the team.
Nope.
All right, that's it.
I need to hear it.
-Hear what?
-[chuckling] Oh, you know what.
What? [sighs] Oh, come on.
Do it.
[sighs] Ba.
With feeling.
[bleats]
[all bleating]
[gasps] What?
[bleating echoes]
[bleats]
[bleating continues]
[screams]
What is that noise?
Give me that!
[bleating continues]
Jett...
-Fillmore.
Your head is so green--
Some of us have
a game to play tomorrow.
Keep it down.
Uh, Jett, Jett.
What?
Um, I was hoping, up to you,
I could get
a little playing time? Eh?
Oh, that's all?
Mmm? Mmm?
Just a little time
on the court?
Oh, kiddo.
All you had to do was ask.
Really?
[triumphant music playing]
[Chuck] And we're back at
the Sunken City Cave,
where stalactites
are falling from the ceiling,
and the Thorns are at risk of
falling out of
playoff contention.
[crowd chanting]
Marshy! Marshy! Marshy!
Whoa! Hey!
[yelps]
[squeaks, burps]
[all cheering]
[grunting]
-[groans]
-[whistle blows]
-Foul. Number three, Fillmore.
-Are you serious right now?
Now you blow the whistle?
One more word
and it's a technical!
Why don't you
take that whistle... [growls]
...and stick it right up
your cloaca.
-[gasps]
-[whistle blows]
Did she just say "cloaca"?
Can you say that on TV?
Well, it's as close as
you can get to saying butth--
[horn honking]
[groans] We could've come back!
I could have won this one.
[sighs]
-[growls]
-[gasps]
-Get up.
-[Olivia] Oh, no.
-This feels bad.
-What are you waiting for?
O-Oh, my gosh. [gasps]
You're putting me in?
[growls]
You think I want to?
I don't have a choice.
Otherwise we forfeit the game.
[yelps]
[stammers]
They're putting in Will!
[both] They're putting in Will!
What?
Hey, it's bedtime. I thoug
I told you kids to--
Things are starting to get ugly
for the Thorns.
You are the authority
on ugly, Chuck!
[children chanting]
Will, Will, Will, Will, Will.
Oh, scoot over.
I gotta watch this.
Just remember, an opportunity
like this is fleeting.
But public humiliation,
that lives forever.
Really?
That's your pep talk?
What? I... [sighs]
I haven't coached in a while.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little out of practice.
-[Will] Who says that?
-The whole planet's watching.
Oh. That's worse.
Don't listen to me.
[Rusty]
What a beautiful moment.
The first small
to play in Roar.
Yo, are you guarding me
or my shoelaces?
I knew jerseys shrunk
in the wash,
but I didn't know
the players did too! Aw.
You're gonna end up
roadkill, kid.
-[chuckles]
-[groans, panting]
Yo, Archie! Pick left!
-Switch it up!
-Hey, goat, good looking out!
[Chuck]
Archie with a big block.
-I got it. I got it.
-[Rusty] And Lenny recovers.
[rumbling]
[Chuck] Will Harris is
heading down the court.
Lenny! Hey, hey! I'm over here.
I'm open. I'm open.
[Rusty]
Lenny looking for somebody,
-anyone who's not a goat.
-[Will] Lenny!
[Chuck]
Nowhere to go but Harris.
[Rusty] Lenny really doesn't
wanna throw that pass!
Let's go!
[grunts]
[Will] No, no, no, no, no, no.
[panting]
-[both growling]
-Uh...
Shoot it, kid!
[groaning, distorted]
[panting, distorted]
[ball bouncing, distorted]
[groans]
[snarls]
[both] Will just scored!
[Chuck] Will Harris becomes
the first small
ever to score a point in Roar!
[triumphant music playing]
-Take it back on D.
-[whistle blows]
Did he just...
[lion roars]
-[Chuck] Too easy!
-Hey!
-Did I upset the little goat?
-[crowd cheering]
[announcer]
Who wants goat tears?
[Mane] ♪ Goat tears
You'll be crying goat tears ♪
-[crowd booing]
-What? Oh, come on.
Will! Hey, Will!
Run Eagle 24.
Thorns! Let's huddle up.
What do we do?
W-What are we gonna do?
Coach wants us to run Eagle 24.
We all know the play?
Uh, no.
-I do.
-I've eaten 24 eagles.
Excuse me, what?
What?
Okay, Lenny.
It's just you and me.
I'm feeling something.
I can't even describe it.
It's like I'm jittery.
-Yeah. That's adrenaline.
-I kind of like it.
Put the ball in play,
or I'm calling a delay of game.
-Okay. Let's do this.
-[whistle blows]
Run whatever play
you want, goat.
I'm locking you down.
-Come on, kid.
-[crowd cheering]
[dramatic music playing]
Will! [caws]
[grunts]
[buzzer sounds]
[Rusty] Thorns win!
Yeah! We just did that!
["Light It Up" playing]
-Lenny, yeah!
-All right! Yeah!
Smalls in the building!
Harris might be a small,
but he came up big!
-[children] Yeah!
-Yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
I'm so happy, I could cry.
Come on, Gerald. Let me see it.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah! Let's go!
Oh, yeah!
-Night, night, baby!
-No!
-Anxious happy energy!
-Yeah!
Anxious happy energy!
[team members chanting]
Roots run deep! Roots run deep!
[chuckles] What did I tell you?
He's got it!
Come on, Jett. We won.
Who wants to throw Dennis?
[music ends]
-[bleats]
-[crowd cheers]
It's like they say, Chuck.
You mess with the goat,
you get a stalactite
to the face.
That's not a catchphrase.
Get off my cloaca, Chuck!
[upbeat music playing]
[Jett] Whatever. Whatever.
I mean, I scored 33,
but who's keeping track?
[chuckling]
What...
Is it lame to search yourself?
It is. [laughs] I know.
I can't help myself.
Yo, goat. Nice work tonight.
You wanna join?
-Who, me?
-Come on.
Get to know your teammates
a little.
We don't bite.
-Well, Modo does sometimes.
-[rasps]
Just get in here.
We're extending an
olive branch here.
Well, I am grabbing
that olive branch. [chuckles]
[groans]
All right, ante up.
Don't be shy now, rook.
Shy? This kid's got ice
in his veins, raining treys.
-[chuckles]
-It was just one trey.
Honestly, when Jett
crashed out of the game,
I thought it was over.
Oh, for sure.
But the goat came through.
My guy!
I didn't even need
my bucket tonight.
This is so cool!
-[team members chuckling]
-[sighs]
All right. All right.
Uh...
Uh, should we ask
Jett to play?
Hey! You trying to ruin
the one piece of fun we got?
[Olivia] We won without Jett.
I can't believe we're actually
talking like this.
She could be listening.
["Meow" playing]
What? Why?
When we win, she likes to
be the one that won the win.
She's a winner, and she's going
to get us to the playoffs.
[chuckles]
We got lucky for one game.
Let's not go mad.
I appreciate the optimism,
but look at this team.
We got Coach Dennis
at the helm.
I think he dies
when he sleeps.
[snoring]
Me? I'm just trying to focus
on my sweet baby angels.
-Incoming! [giggles]
-[farts]
[screaming]
-We saved your life.
-[giggling]
-Oh, my gosh.
-Everybody just sees me
as a tall rebound robot.
At a certain point,
I just checked out.
I started finding
other ways to be creative.
Lenny is a rapper.
Ah, Olivia, stop trying
to put me on front stree
You know it's nothing
I take too seriously.
[hip-hop playing]
[Lenny caws]
Okay, maybe I take it
a little seriously.
And I'm a bust. Maybe
the biggest in Roar history.
Come on now, Liv.
That ain't true.
It is. You can say it.
What else do you call
a number-one pick
whose biggest claim to fame
is being on
someone else's poster?
Olivia?
Listen. Point is, this squad
is a bunch of head cases,
has-beens,
and whatever the heck Modo is.
Modo is icon.
All right, Care Bear.
Bets are in.
What you got?
[dramatic music playing]
I fold.
Ah! Uno reverse.
-Uno, Uno, Uno! Uno, Uno, Uno.
-Modo. Wrong game!
Yeah, they're
the absolute worst.
-Oh. Oh, hi!
-Oh, hi, Flo.
-Hey, Flo!
-Hi, Flo.
-[Archie] Hey, boss.
-Hi, piglet.
Ugh. Hi, Modo.
Anyways... [blowing]
Great team win last night.
Socials are blowing up, and
I've got some exciting news.
Hey, is Jett there?
-Jett?
-What?
-Jett!
Oh, hi. You know that
Jett promo tomorrow?
Well, now you're all
gonna be in it.
[all cheering]
-Oh, yeah. Oh, this is dope.
-[growling]
["Meow" playing]
[song ends]
[dramatic music playing]
[commentator] In Vineland,
our roots run deep.
Vineland didn't just invent
the game of roarball.
We define it.
No one gets by me in the lane.
I don't play the long game.
I play the tall game.
Can't catch me on a fast break.
[chuckles]
I make you feel weird
and you're not sure why.
And I'm the best in the game.
[commentator]
It's the end of one era
and the beginning of another.
It's my time now.
And now, it's time to
pass the torch to the new GO--
[groans] GOAT!
[stammering]
[retching]
I'm sorry. I can't.
I can't. I... This...
-My body is rejecting the word.
-[director] Cut!
You know what,
let's just take five.
Cut! Jett, baby,
what's the problem?
The problem is I'm the GOAT.
I'm not passing the torch
'cause I'm still playing.
[blows]
It's just a promo.
It's a play on words.
He's a goat but also
wants to be the GOAT.
Just say the lines.
Are we all okay with this?
Now, I want to see
a show of paws.
Raise 'em up!
Who is okay with this?
[chuckles] Oh, everybody? Okay.
Hey, Maximus, let's pick
it up from "they define it
-You got it, boss.
-[beeping]
[clears throat]
[deep voice]
Vineland didn't just
invent the game of roarball.
We define it.
I block every shot.
I'm unstoppable.
I think.
And I think there is
a power struggle happening.
-The end of one era...
-I'm the GOAT.
...and the beginning of another
that's even better.
It's my time--
-No, it's not.
-Cut!
-Just say the line, Jett.
-[bell ringing]
-No! It's not true.
-I don't think you understand
the difference between
figurative and literal.
It's a double goat meaning.
I don't care.
I'm not saying it!
-And he's not saying it either!
-[sighs]
And y'all don't even think
about saying it. Capisce?
[Maximus] Vineland didn't just
invent the game of roarball.
-We define it.
-[sobbing]
I just wanna be a good dad.
I just wanna blow minds
with sick rhymes.
Whoever memes my beak,
you will be hearing from
my lawyer.
I don't even know
the rules of roarball.
I'm the GOAT.
Always have been,
always will be.
Not some little goat guy.
-It's a single goat meaning.
-[director] Cut!
-Cut, cut!
-[bell ringing]
Look, since you're not
gonna say the line,
why don't you just give us
a little "Baa."
Oh, I am not saying that.
Why do I bother you so much?
[growls]
You just got here, son.
Who even are you?
I'm the one who stepped up
when you fouled out.
We finally won,
and you weren't even
on the court.
-[gasps]
-[feedback screeches]
Now I feel weird.
Is this how
I make everyone feel?
[growls, sighs]
You know what, superstar?
This looks like
it's your promo now.
'Cause I'm out of here. Yeah.
-Good luck selling tickets.
-[door opens, slams]
Jett! Wait.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to--
I didn't sign up
for that, all right?
Come on, Jett,
it's just a promo.
It gets fans hyped
for our game!
But it's not.
It's how everyone treats me.
They all want me to
pass the torch,
but I'm not done!
There she is. Hey, Mom...
I'm still here!
I'm still playing!
We're still waiting on
that Claw, Fillmore.
You're better off
on the bench.
What?
[fan 1] I love you, Jett!
I just want my car.
Where is my driver?
[fan 2] Jett! Over here!
-Follow me.
-[fan 3] Jett Fillmore!
[fan 4] Hey, Jett.
Why do you not win anymore?
["Grandmaster" playing]
[pedestrian 1] Hey, watch it!
-[Will gulps]
-[growls]
[pedestrian 2] Excuse me.
[all groaning]
This way.
Whoa. This kid can move.
-[music continues]
-[groans]
[roars]
[music ends]
[both chuckling]
I've never broken
the law before.
[grunts]
I feel so alive.
I actually paid for
both of our rides.
I just wanted to see you sweat.
[chuckles, groans]
[chuckles]
[melancholy music playing]
It was so messed up back there.
I mean, they act like
you've been losing forever!
I don't know
what's wrong with them,
b-but I remember
the Furball game.
That was amazing!
You scored 70 points!
Well, you know why they call it
the Furball game, right?
Because I choked.
I missed the last shot.
We didn't make the Claw.
Ever since then, Vineland's got
no love for Jett Fillmore.
No love for Jett Fillmore?
[stammers]
You're seriously gonna listen
to a couple of haters?
Where's the lie? Even I get it.
[announcer] Next stop,
Vineland City Center.
Okay. Get up.
We're getting off right here.
[trumpets]
[dings]
-[patron] Hey, there he is!
-[all clamoring]
Oh.
You come to pick up
some extra shifts?
Ah. [chuckles]
I see you got jokes.
[Daryl] Come back empty-handed?
You said you'd get me
Jett Fillmore's autograph.
[whispers] Oh, my gosh.
It's Jett Fillmore.
-[all gasping]
-What's up, y'all?
Jett said
she'd never tried the pie,
so I figured we'd pull up.
[chuckles, gasps]
This is...
[uplifting music playing]
Whoa.
[Will] Not bad, huh?
Wait, is that
my high school jersey?
Dang, y'all are some
crazy stalkers.
[all chuckling]
[chuckling]
What do we have here? No way.
Is that you? [chuckles, sighs]
[chuckles] Hey, you wanna
meet the others?
My grandpappy came here
from afar
to help build
the Greenhouse. Yes.
That's little me right there
in my diaper.
W-Wow.
We're gonna name
our baby after you, Jett!
We're hoping she'll grow up
to be just like you.
Aw. Cute egg.
Check this out!
When I move my shoulders,
it looks like you're dunking.
Oh... [retches] Yeah.
Um... It definitely looks like
I am doing something.
[bell dings]
[Jett] Okay, so
we're down by two, right?
I'm nauseous.
It's like that every time
I go to open my mouth,
it's like... [gasping]
...here it comes.
I can't even see straight.
I knew it! I knew it!
I could tell something was off.
How did you get so sick?
Look, I'm not gonna say
it's true,
but I will say the delivery guy
was wearing a Magma jersey.
-[all gasping]
-Coinkydink? You decide.
[Will] Drumroll, please.
-[drumming]
-[swallows]
-[all cheering]
-Right? Right? I told you.
Oh, snap. The Fillmore 1's?
Where did you get these?
A collector
never reveals her secrets.
[chuckles] Just kidding.
I got 'em from the store
when they came out.
I've been looking everywhe
for these.
O-Okay, how much
do you want for 'em?
Are you kidding me?
Your money's no good here.
They're your shoe.
Just take 'em.
No. No.
Just bring back a Claw.
[purrs] Deal.
[patrons] Bye, Jett!
Later, y'all.
How did you know about
that spot?
I, uh...
I go there for the pie.
It delivers every time.
-Oh.
-[chuckles]
You were the delivery boy.
Yeah, yeah. [exhales]
Was that a little too obvious?
Okay.
[exhales]
I mean...
[sighs]
The real reason
I know the diner
is because my mom
used to work there.
-She was a huge Thorns fan.
-[Mom kissing]
Mom.
That's for every year.
[kisses]
Happy birthday, Will.
[chuckles]
Baby, you know you could wish
for anything, so dream big.
You're not just going to
play roarball.
You're gonna change
the game. [kisses]
Dream big.
-[inhales, blows]
-[patrons cheering]
[Will] Then, she got sick.
[blows]
And Vineland stepped up for me.
Roarball was where I went
to get out of my head
and just... play.
Y-You know?
And everyone thought
I was tripping
when I said I wanted to be
a roarball player.
Everybody.
Except for my mom.
And I want her to be right.
[car door opens]
You got a lot of
good folks behind you.
So do you.
-[sighs]
-[car door closes]
See you at practice tomorrow.
[Jett purring]
Hey, yo. It's Mane season.
Oh, no. Here we go.
And you know, man,
just at the barbershop
with P-Dogg and Boogie.
Let's get into it.
A lot of naysayers
out there, folks,
been talkin' about
this big game the goat had.
Puttin' up a whole
three points. He's trash.
Thorns are trash!
And it ain't just the goat
that's wack.
The whole team is cooked!
-They trash.
-Mm-mmm.
Someone needs to
shut this clown up
-once and for all.
-[phone chimes]
Hold up! Looks like we got a
special chat request. [laughs]
It's the grandmama herself,
Jett Fillmore.
Yo, yo, yo!
Mane is on live with Jett!
What? Let me see that.
[swallows]
[gasps]
No way, bro-dents.
Do you know what?
I'm just surprised
you even know how to
use your phone
for anything other than
reading a menu
with the flashlight.
I'm surprised you can talk
with teeth like that.
Your tongue over there
lookin' like it's in jail.
"Let me out. Let me out."
[all] Oh!
[chuckling] Jett's got bars.
I've been in the league
five years,
already got two Claws.
How many Claws you got?
-Nada. [exclaims, cackles]
-Ball don't lie.
Ball don't lie.
Well, that's about
to change.
I don't know if you saw
our last game,
but Will is
shooting straight fire.
Archie is a beast,
Olivia got her confidence back,
Lenny's a stopper
-and Modo is an icon.
-Hey!
The Thorns are about to win
our next eight games
and then, yeah,
we're coming for the Claw.
[all gasping]
[chuckling] Girl, you crazy.
Only thing crazy is
that Clydesdale hair
that you got sewn into
your head.
The textures don't match.
[growls]
Drag him, Jett.
[chuckling]
Oh!
Textures don't match.
Hey, guys, don't diss the hair.
You know I get sensitive.
Oh!
Jett!
Wait till I get off this live.
[laughs] Hmm.
You know what,
I hope you make a run
so I can wreck you,
just like I wrecked
that baby goat at the Cage.
Until then, keep
Will and the Thorns
out your mouth.
These roots run deep!
Fillmore out.
[all chanting]
Roots run deep! Roots run deep!
Roots run deep!
[inhales, exhales]
-[all cheering]
-[chuckling]
Yeah, mama!
[chuckles]
You said some
pretty nice stuff about us.
I'm wondering why.
Are you feeling okay?
It's the first time
I've been tagged
in something that
didn't make me cry.
I don't trust it.
Did you mean it?
Look, I meant
every word that I said.
I really do need y'all.
And it's time
I finally acknowledged
that I've got some
really good folks behind me.
-[chuckling]
-Yeah.
Really?
To show you how serious I am,
I'm ready to
shake some things up.
I'm officially naming Dennis
the new head coach
of the Thorns.
[uplifting music playing]
But I'm already head coach.
I know. But now, it's, lik
for real this time.
You're gonna be head coach.
Only coach.
[chuckles]
The team is yours, Dennis.
-[all cheering]
-Yeah, man!
Let's go, baby. Give it up.
My therapist said this day
would never come. Uh...
Just give me a second.
Dennis, get it together.
Get it together.
Get. It. Together.
[grunting, screams]
[panting]
I've been watching, learning,
waiting for this day.
-I'm scared.
-[both] We like it.
We are going to rip the heart
out of this league
and make 'em look at it.
[chuckles] Nice.
Welcome to
Dennis's world of pain.
[cackling]
Archie, you don't have to worry
about your little girls
growing up
with violent tendencies.
Charge! [giggling]
They've gone full-tilt
365-days-a-year psychopath.
Actually, it's 364.
We take Christmas off.
Stop thinking of yourself
as an enforcer.
You're a protector.
Your teammates are like
your daughters too.
Protect them.
[Archie] Hey, hands off
my beautiful daughter.
Good looking out, Archie.
Wait, what did you
just call me?
Lenny, team after team
used you for your height
and threw you away.
So you lost your drive.
Ten teams in ten years, Coach.
Well, this team has your back.
So stick your neck out
for them.
Now tear the roof off
this mother!
[squawks]
[gasps]
[Lenny] Bang!
Nice one, Lenny.
That's my squad.
Ooh, I kind of like that.
Olivia.
-One second. I'm just...
-[keyboard clicking]
[Dennis] Seriously,
give me your phone.
-Oh, no.
-You are never seeing it again.
[whimpers]
Another phone?
Where are you getting
all these phones?
Olivia, get your head out of
the phone and into the game!
[groans] Ugh.
[rasps]
[chuckles]
You were drafted number one
for a reason.
The only thing
holding you back is you.
You are still that bird.
I am that bird.
Will. Jett.
[chuckling] I'm gonna coach
the scat out of you.
-Dennis, there's kids here.
-[both] Scat! Scat! Scat!
Jett, remember
these three words,
"Pass the ball."
-Like, let the ball go?
-Jett.
You mean share?
With the others?
I don't think this lesson
is for me.
-Trust your team.
-[Will] Open!
-[Dennis] Jett, pass the ball.
-[whistle blows]
[groans]
It's harder than it looks.
[Will] I'm open.
-[Dennis] Pass it!
-What? [meows, whimpers]
Jett.
I got it. I got it.
-Pass the ball, Jett.
-[Jett] No, no, no, no.
Dennis. No, no, Dennis.
[meows] No, no, no. Dennis!
[growls]
[groans]
Yes! Yes!
Now just do that
500,000 more times.
You, big hairy guy.
Block everything that
the kid throws your way.
And you,
that's 12 feet of grizzly.
Figure it out.
Blocked.
-Blocked.
-Dang.
Hey.
Blocked.
-[exclaims] Blocked.
-[whistle blows]
Will, you gotta find a way
to get your shot over him.
And Modo--
Wait, wait.
Say it with your mind.
Message!
Yeah, yeah.
[grunts] Received.
If you do all this,
you'll be more than a team.
You'll be a unit. Unstoppable.
[team members] Roots run deep!
"Goat Tears" is wack,
-and I can't let it stand.
-[hip-hop music playing]
So, Will, I've prepared
a little something
to say "thank you"
for pushing us this far.
♪ That's my squad
That's my squad ♪
Here you go, Ms. Fillmore.
Can I get a picture?
[camera shutter clicks]
♪ Shout out to my squad
Throw me the alley-oop ♪
♪ I'm always at the top... ♪
No way.
Nice to meet you, Theo.
And this is for your dad.
♪ We not horsin' round
With you, okay ♪
Uno reverse.
You like that, Modo?
Give me some.
[singsongy] Uno.
[Lenny] ♪ Sorry, horsey
Gotta roast ya ♪
♪ Looks like Mr. Pony
Turnin' into Mr. Phony ♪
Will.
♪ Lenny G the one and only
And I always got my homeys ♪
Slamalamadingdong!
♪ That's my squad, hey
That's my squad, hey ♪
Olivia.
♪ I love my squad, hey ♪
Yo, Lenny!
♪ Shout out to my squad
Throw me the alley-oop ♪
♪ I'm always at the top ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm taller than
The hoop ♪
-Horns on, everybody.
-[exclaims]
[Chuck] Thorns have really
found their groove.
And is it me, or is Modo
looking different these days?
[Rusty] Oh, yeah.
He's a thirst trap, Chuck.
Go long for my skin.
Marry me, Modo.
No, marry me! [groans]
-Whoo!
-[crowd] Thorns! Thorns!
[Chuck] The Thorns punch
their ticket to the Roar Four
and are heading
to the playoffs.
[Rusty]
What a turnaround, Chuck!
If I were Mane, I'd be shaking
in my horseshoes
'cause the Thorns
are coming for him.
[Lenny] ♪ Looks like Mr. Pony
Turnin' into Mr. Phony... ♪
Do we have a deal? [chuckles]
Good.
Coach Dennis,
how about a comment
on this team's
epic turnaround?
-How's it feel, Dennis?
-[song ends]
It feels like victory!
["Meets The Eye" playing]
♪ It's more than
Meets the eye ♪
[chuckles]
Yay!
Okay, didn't know an ostri
could get that fly.
I see you, Olivia.
You know what they say,
birds of a feather
look fly together.
[chuckles]
Archie's a whole vibe.
[chuckles] Yeah, buddy.
I look good and I play good.
[laughs]
If Modo were any more of
a snack, he'd eat himself.
Love it. Love it.
Uh...
[stammers]
I'll be right back.
[song ends]
Uh, anyone know where Jett is?
I'll go get her.
[announcer]
From the Vineland Thorns,
at guard, Jett Fillmore!
I sold this team.
The new Thorns are relocating
to Sunken City.
I'm sorry, what?
You're joking.
[chuckles]
Oh, I never joke about
money, honey.
I brought Will onto this team
to put butts in seats,
but I didn't expect
for you to actually win.
I'm selling
while the getting's good.
[stammers] What's gonna
happen to the team?
Oh, they're all gone, sweetie.
[chuckles] Cleaning house.
And as for you... [chuckles]
I made sure the new owners knew
all about your worn-out body.
And surprise, surprise,
they weren't about to
waste money
on an old, broken-down player
who's never gonna win a Claw!
[Jett growls]
Oh.
And tell the team to clean out
their lockers after y'all lose.
Enjoy your
early retirement, Jett.
Hey, good luck
out there tonight.
[chuckles, slurps]
[Jett sighs]
Jett, Flo sold the Thorns?
You listening in
on my conversations now?
We need to go tell the team.
[Jett] No,
we'll tell them after the game.
If we tell them now,
they'll fall apart.
This affects all of us.
Whatever's coming,
we got to face it together.
Who's team captain here?
You or me?
Jett.
After the game.
[Chuck]
Welcome to the Cryosphere.
Tonight,
the Shivers face the Thorns
in the semi-final game.
The winner marches
triumphantly to the finals
to battle for a championship
and eternal glory.
The loser? Banished to
the cold void of history.
This is not just a game.
It is a reckoning.
[dramatic music playing]
[growls]
[groans]
[grunts, growls]
Lenny,
are you trying to get traded?
Hey, hey, Jett, you good?
Focus on the game.
Don't worry about it.
We'll get the next one.
-Olivia.
-[Olivia gasps]
One more pass.
Next time you think
about shooting, don't.
[gasps] I'm sorry, Jett.
-[Chuck] And that's the half.
-[buzzer sounds]
Maybe we should
tell them now.
After the game.
[panting]
[opponent] Don't hurt
yourself, grandma.
Catch! Yeah!
[roars]
[Chuck] Oh! The icebreaker!
And Harris is slow to get up.
So much for that Claw.
[chuckles]
[Will] Thanks.
[Chuck] Thorns are down by 15
late in the fourth quarter.
[Rusty] It is not looking good
for their playoff hopes.
What is going on out there?
Jett, tell them.
They need to know.
What did I say?
Flo sold the team
to Sunken City.
None of us are going with it.
Can she even do that?
Is that even allowed?
We were playing well.
We just started jelling.
-She sold our team?
-[Olivia] There are rules.
[fan 1] I thought you had
a championship.
[fan 2] Could have been
a legend, instead...
[Flo] Broken-down player
who's never gonna win a Claw!
Just get me the ball.
I'm not going out like this.
Don't you mean "we"?
I know that look.
[growls]
What do you think you're doing?
[Chuck] That's two.
Thorns down by ten.
Come on.
-We got to D up.
-[grunts]
Somebody get a body on her.
Come on.
[growls]
Pass!
[Chuck]
We've seen this before, Rusty.
It's the Jett Fillmore
show now.
Jett with the pull-up.
Thorns down eight.
[panting]
[groans]
Heads up!
[Chuck]
That deficit is cut to five.
It's a one-point game.
Ball! Now!
[Chuck]
It all comes down to this!
-Archie!
-Give me that, small.
-[Will] Boost me!
-[groans]
[grunts]
[Rusty]
Will Harris for the win!
-[Jett] Yeah!
-[buzzer sounds]
[Chuck] Thorns win! Thorns win!
They're headed to the Claw!
[pants] So it looks like
we're going to the...
to the finals.
Wow. I-I'm done.
Team's sold anyway.
Come on, girls.
I'm not sticking around
for this.
Modo as well.
[melancholy music playing]
[Will sighs]
You used to be
my favorite player.
Until today.
[Rusty] What a turn of events.
The Thorns have
a shot at the Claw,
but Vineland has
lost their team.
[Chuck] I'll tell you, Rusty,
I would hate to be a Thorns fan
right about now.
["Don't Dream It's Over"
playing]
♪ There is freedom within ♪
♪ There is freedom without ♪
♪ Try to catch the deluge
In a paper cup ♪
♪ There's a battle ahead ♪
♪ Many battles are lost ♪
♪ But you'll never see
The end of the road ♪
♪ While you're traveling
With me ♪
♪ Hey now, hey now ♪
♪ Don't dream it's over ♪
♪ When the world comes in ♪
♪ They come, they come ♪
♪ To build a wall between us ♪
♪ We know they won't win ♪
♪ Now I'm towing my car ♪
♪ There's a hole in the roof ♪
♪ My possessions
Are causing me suspicion ♪
♪ But there's no proof ♪
♪ In the paper today ♪
♪ Tales of war and of waste ♪
♪ But you turn right over
To the TV page ♪
♪ Hey now, hey now ♪
♪ Don't dream it's over ♪
[song ends]
Come on. Let's go!
-[pants]
-[bleats]
I got it! [grunts]
[all cheering]
[Grizz] Smalls can ball.
Whew! [chuckles]
Yeah!
[scoffs] No way.
Wait, is that...
[all] Hey, Will.
Goat? Ball.
Yo, shouldn't you be getting
ready to face the Magma?
Did you not watch the game?
I don't think Jett wants
to play with us anymore.
I'm willing to bet she does.
Hey. Can we talk?
I'm busy.
-No, he's not.
-Come on, come on.
-Give... Give me the ball.
-Not happening. My ball now.
I came to say I'm-I'm sorry.
Okay. Well, you did it. So...
Please, just hear me out?
[inhales, sighs]
I want to win.
I want to hold up that Claw
and feel what it's like
to be one of the greats.
When Flo said all that stu
about me being washed up,
it just... it-it...
it just got in my head.
And I couldn't let it go
because deep down,
deep, deep down,
I'm scared she's right.
And I just panicked. [pants]
And I did you all so dirty.
And I'm so...
[inhales sharply] ...sorry.
You know,
I really thought that
if I was holding a Claw
at the end of the day,
it wouldn't matter
how I got it.
But when you think about it,
that's kind of
all that matters.
[chuckles]
That was a really good apology.
But you know,
you still owe the diner a Claw.
It's gonna be hard to win
without a team.
I might know a few folks.
-[doorbell rings]
-[footsteps thud]
-[child 1] Dad.
-[child 2] Daddy clown!
-Oh, thank God.
-[twins clamoring]
These girls are crazy.
Get me out of here.
Quick, start the car!
[tapping on window]
-[squeaks]
-Yo.
[Olivia chirping]
Sup, Olivia?
Come on. We've got
a game to win.
Yes!
[mysterious music playing]
[growls, hisses]
[chortles, rasps]
[suspenseful music playing]
[crowd cheering]
[music continues]
[Chuck] This is what dreams
are made of, Rusty.
-[blusters]
-Teams become champions.
Players become legends.
-♪ Let's go ♪
-♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Gimme the ball
Gimme the ball, yeah ♪
-♪ Let's go! ♪
-♪ Oh, I'm 'bout to... ♪
-Go, Thorns!
-The best day of my life.
I can feel myself
getting invested.
Who cares? I'm here for it.
Break my heart, kiddo!
Come on, Will. Let's go!
[all] Go, Thorns! Go, Thorns!
[Chuck] Tonight, Jett and Mane
will finally answer
the question,
-who is the GOAT?
-On three.
-One, two, three.
-[all] Roots run deep!
-[crowd cheering]
-[song ends]
[Rusty] And here we go, Chuck.
Unbelievable!
Mane Attraction
gets the tip over Lenny.
[pants, grunts]
[groans]
[Chuck] Mane drills one home,
sending a strong message
to the Thorns.
[chuckles]
You're too small. [spits]
Come on, Will.
Show 'em who's too small.
[whistle blows]
Eyes on me. [growls]
[Rusty]
Jett with the sweet pass.
Thorns respond.
-[all cheering]
-Yeah!
[Chuck] As the first quarter
comes to a close,
it's still anyone's game.
[whinnies] We should be
frying these fools.
Take 'em out if you have to,
but hold on to that lead.
[all grunting]
[Rusty] Harris on a break!
Nuh-uh! Not today!
-Will, watch out!
-Huh?
[groans]
[Chuck] Ow! Hard hit on Jett.
-No foul call.
-[buzzer sounds]
What?
[groans, shrieks]
[inhales sharply]
Oh, no.
[grunting, panting]
This injury could
take you out permanently
if you put any more weight
on this leg.
[groans, sniffles]
I'm sorry, y'all.
Jett. I didn't mean
for you to get hurt.
Hey, hey.
It's not your fault.
But I think I'm done.
What are we gonna do?
We can't win without Jett.
What? Aw, we're
all thinking it.
[melancholy music playing]
[sighs]
Look, "roots run deep,"
that's more than just a cheer.
You guys have no idea
what you mean to this city.
My mom told me to dream big.
And for Vineland,
there is no dream bigger
than bringing home a Claw.
This might be the last time
Vineland Thorns ever play.
And we ain't
gonna go out like this.
Yeah, you heard the rook.
[inhales, growls]
Let's dream big.
Is that-- Is that Jett?
-Did she just--
-Yeah, Jett!
[crowd exclaiming, cheering]
[crowd chanting]
Jett, Jett, Jett!
[Chuck] A well-deserved
standing ovation
for the legendary
Jett Fillmore.
[chanting continues]
Welcome back, GOAT.
[crowd chanting rapidly]
Jett! Jett! Jett!
Archie.
[grunts]
[Chuck] Harris is on a tear.
The Thorns are all tied up.
-Olivia!
-I got this.
[roars]
[cackles]
I am that bird.
[grunts]
[majestic music playing]
[both] She can fly!
I can fly!
She can fly?
[whinnies]
[Chuck] Olivia Burke
just posterized Mane!
I am losing my mind here!
-Olivia!
-[all cheering]
-That's right.
-Go, Livvy!
[all] Go, Thorns! We can do it!
[Rusty] Smalls ball!
Ostriches fly!
These are the Thorns
we came to see!
Look who's the
poster child now.
[grunts, whinnies]
-[blusters]
-[whistle blows]
Time out, Magma.
Oh, word of advice?
Stay off social media.
We gotta turn this around now.
-Where my Maniacs at?
-[all chanting] Mane!
Uh-oh, I think we've got
some seismic activity.
Just listen to that crowd.
-They're going crazy.
-Oh, yeah!
[Rusty] Let's go!
[ominous music playing]
-Archie's trapped. No way out.
-I know the feeling, Rusty.
-Whoa! And up goes Lenny.
-[groans]
[Mane chuckling]
Jett can't save you now.
[chuckles]
[Rusty] Ooh. Hard foul by Mane.
-What?
-You gotta call that!
The zebra and the horse
are working together.
-[all] Boo!
-Come on! That's a foul.
[groans]
Really? That's how
you want to win? Huh?
What you gonna do
about it, small?
Hey, Mane!
He's not a small.
He's a medium!
-[referee] Hey, break it up!
-[whistle blows]
Let me at him! Let me at him!
-Relax!
-[whistle blows]
-[groans]
-Keep your hooves
off my teammates.
Get him, Daddy!
Make him bleed!
That's not
what you want to see.
Speak for yourself.
Flagrant two.
Number 34, ejected.
Are you kidding me?
Mane started it.
-Where's his foul?
-[Mane] Cry about it.
[Chuck] The rules state
Thorns need five players
-or they forfeit.
-Hit me again.
[bell dings]
[panting] Okay, okay.
I haven't played
since my rec-league days,
but I guess I could--
[grunts]
[snarls, growling]
Put me in, Coach.
I got a game to win.
-[laughs]
-[growls]
Jett, you can barely walk.
No. We can't let you do this.
You'll just make it worse.
You think they bought it?
[all gasp]
Um, I do.
I think we have about three
seconds before they catch on.
But that's all we need.
You all ready?
I've been trying to run a play
like this all season,
but some hothead
kept interrupting me.
That's a great play.
Yeah. It was worth the wait.
[all] Roots run deep!
[Chuck] Thorns are down by 2
with 20 seconds on the clock.
[Rusty] Jett's gonna lay it all
on the line. What a competitor!
Listen up. Double-team her.
Triple-team her if you have to.
Do not let her out
of your sight.
[Chuck] Jett's fighting an
injury. The court is unstable.
Do you still want her
taking the final shot?
[Rusty] With fire and brimstone
bringing judgment and wrath
to us all, I want Fillmore!
[groans]
[grunting]
[all groaning, distorted]
[climactic music playing]
Ah!
[grunts]
[snarls]
[growling]
-[leg crunches]
-[whimpers]
[whinnies]
[roars]
[both growling]
[growls]
Will!
[panting]
Come on. Get past me.
I don't have to.
[groans]
[buzzer sounds]
[music continues]
-[all cheering]
-[triumphant music playing]
Our bestie just won the Claw.
That's my boy!
Hold me, Daryl. [giggles]
[Rusty] For the first time
in 50 years,
the Vineland Thorns
are champions!
Miracles can happen, folks.
[chuckling] I love this game.
And I love you, Rusty.
[sobbing]
I love you too, Chuckles.
[uplifting music playing]
-Attaboy, Will! Mwah!
-[all exclaiming]
Honey!
Let's have another
dozen kids. [chuckles]
Ha-ha!
Ten years, ten teams,
one Claw, baby!
We are champions!
-Daddy!
You were so cool.
Daddy was pretty cool, right?
I was like... [roars]
[both] We love you. Mwah.
[chuckles] I love you girls.
-[rasping]
-[twins giggling]
[blusters]
Hey, Mane. Good game.
Let me help you up.
Hey, uh, your hair is on fire.
What?
Oh, no. No. No.
Not the hair! [sobbing]
-[Jett] Will!
-Jett.
We're champions, baby.
Oh, Jett! We did it!
We actually did it!
No, you did it.
Looks like Moms was right.
[groans]
-J-Jett, you okay? You good?
-I'm fine.
I'm fine. I just can't
feel my legs... [chuckling]
...but I'm a champion, baby.
[laughs] Never thought
I'd see the day
Jett Fillmore passed the ball.
[both] Security!
[Flo] Hold up, sucka.
Playtime?
Should we destroy?
[both] Destroy! [giggling]
[Flo] Do you know who I am?
Hey, you were right
about Will.
He's a great addition
to the team.
Bye, piglet.
[announcer] Introducing
your Roar champions,
the Vineland Thorns!
-[all cheering]
-[upbeat music playing]
Yeah! Let's go, Vineland!
Let's go!
[all cheering]
Horns up, everybody.
Vineland!
I think it's time
they hear from...
-the GOAT.
-[crowd cheering]
[all chanting]
Will! Will! Will!
Medium fries did it!
[all whooping]
[music continues]
-I... I...
-[cheering stops]
I don't even know
what to say right now.
-[sighs] This is crazy.
-[fan] We love you, Will!
Oh, wow, um...
I mean... [scoffs]
I saw Jett play when...
when I was just a kid.
Then I told my mom, I said,
"I'm gonna be just like her."
[atmospheric music playing]
And you know what's crazy?
My mom actually believed it.
She always seemed to know those
kinds of things, you know?
Like she always knew that even
if she couldn't be here for me,
-Vineland would be.
-[crowd cheering]
You delivered for me...
Will done changed the game.
And you always had my back.
[both bleating]
And you inspired me.
[all chuckling]
We brought the Claw home!
[all cheering]
And even if the Thorns
don't have a home
in Vineland anymore...
[crowd booing]
[sobbing]
[blows nose]
...no one can take
this Claw away from us!
[cheering resumes]
Vineland will be
champions forever!
-Modo has something to say!
-[cheering stops]
Thorns staying in Vineland!
[all gasp]
-Modo is team owner.
-[crowd exclaiming]
Wait. How?
[dramatic music playing]
All in.
[opponent] All in.
A-ha! Uno reverse!
What?
Let me take a look at that.
You're giving this
freak lizard the team?
Wow! This is actually legit.
[chuckling] Modo's my boss.
-That's not good.
-[all whooping]
Yeah, mama!
[rasps, muttering]
-[chuckling] Modo.
-[vocalizing]
[all chuckling]
-[fan 1] Marry me, Modo!
-[fan 2] No, marry me!
You hear that, Vineland?
Looks like the Thorns
are staying!
[all chanting]
Roots run deep! Roots run deep!
[chanting continues]
Roots run deep!
[all bleating]
[chuckles]
[atmospheric music playing]
[Young Will] Thanks, Mom.
["I'm Good" playing]
♪ Whoo! Come on ♪
♪ Oh, what a beautiful day ♪
♪ I'm just so glad I'm alive ♪
♪ I got this smile on my face ♪
♪ 'Cause I opened up my eyes ♪
♪ I found my way
Out that place ♪
♪ I never thought
That I would ♪
♪ See the day I could say
I'm good, I'm good ♪
♪ I'm good with
That old temptation ♪
♪ All the people on the way
That tried to break me ♪
♪ The time I lost that
I tossed out that hourglass ♪
♪ Right now, I ain't
Thinking 'bout none of that ♪
♪ Made amends with the friends
That did me wrong ♪
♪ Let go of all the hurt
I was holding on ♪
♪ Took the cards I was dealt
And started playing right ♪
♪ You found the underdog
And I found the light, oh ♪
♪ I was fighting
Chasing all my lows ♪
♪ With the wrong highs, oh ♪
♪ Now I'm singing me
a brand-new song ♪
♪ And it goes like... ♪
♪ Oh, what a beautiful day ♪
♪ I'm just so glad I'm alive ♪
♪ I've got this smile
On my face ♪
♪ 'Cause I opened up my eyes ♪
♪ I found my way
Out that place ♪
♪ I never thought
That I would ♪
♪ See the day I could say
I'm good, I'm good ♪
♪ I'm good with the path
That I'm walking down ♪
♪ No way, no how
I'ma turn around ♪
♪ See the good in the bad
Life handed me ♪
♪ The broken road that led me
Straight to my family ♪
♪ Made peace
With the broken pieces ♪
♪ Finally made my way
Out the deep end ♪
♪ Some days
I still can't believe it ♪
♪ I'm still living
I'm still breathing, oh ♪
♪ So I'm singing me a brand-new
Song, and it goes like... ♪
♪ Oh, what a beautiful day ♪
♪ I'm just so glad I'm alive ♪
♪ I got this smile on my face ♪
♪ 'Cause I opened up my eyes ♪
♪ I found my way
Out that place ♪
♪ I never thought
That I would ♪
♪ See the day I could say
I'm good, I'm good ♪
♪ Oh, I'm good ♪
♪ I'm good, I'm good ♪
[song ends]
["World Go Round" playing]
["Don't Dream It's Over"
playing]
[song ends]
[atmospheric music playing]
[Mom] Dream big.